<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Byron Donaldson</title>
    <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Byron Donaldson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2024, Byron Donaldson</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://byrondonaldson.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Field Notes - Cincinnati</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/cincinnati/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/cincinnati/</guid>
      <description>Last updated: 30 Apr 2024
Notes: First impressions of Cincinnati (And the USA) As it happens, in the great year of 2024 I have moved to Cincinnati. Nevermind why, that&amp;rsquo;s my business. Anyway, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d put down some field notes from the first couple of months - first impressions and questions and all that - sort of Devon Zuegel on Miami inspired. These are just the passing observations of an ignorant Southern African, don&amp;rsquo;t take them too seriously - no doubt there will be some prize foolishness throughout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interesting questions, for yourself, and others</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/questions/</guid>
      <description>A good question can be a wonderful thing. Well, I thought I might start a collection! To get better at questions, and to probe more deeply into my own skull, for both general psychic inquiries and more specific situations. If you have good ones, please share them with me! This list will be living. (Source/inspiration provided when known/suitable)
  What important truth do very few people agree with you on?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a Personal Running Heatmap in R &amp; Python</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/projects/running/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/projects/running/</guid>
      <description>Making an interactive running map Last updated: Nov 2023
 &amp;ldquo;A race? You&amp;rsquo;ve lost your mind! Jogging is private, you don&amp;rsquo;t jog for an audience.&amp;quot;
Cop 223, Chungking Express
  I have, by now, been running for almost 6 years, cosying up to 17 000 kms. One of the treats of running is as an act of exploration. To explore on foot places you are visiting, a reason to go to a particular place, and to explore closer to home - the area you live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chiloe</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/chiloe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/chiloe/</guid>
      <description>Chiloé &amp;ldquo;So, what next?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Well, we will go to Chiloé. And it will be good.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I thought we were already in Chile?&amp;rdquo;
I was, by now, used to this kind of total, brutish ignorance. After all, my brother had spent the previous two weeks insisting he could speak Spanish by adding dado to the end of English words. And this from a scientist! At any rate, it didn&amp;rsquo;t matter much, the big man had long since given up creative control over the trip to his reclusive younger brother, and a twenty year out of date Lonely Planet guide to Chile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/books/</guid>
      <description>I love finding book lists. Channeling Garfunkel, I&amp;rsquo;m just putting everything - well, since I decided to keep track.   2024-10-26 Rand, Atlas Shrugged 2024-09-09 Russell, The Conquest of Happiness 2024-08-01 Pirsig, Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance 2024-06-23 Suskind, Perfume 2024-06-08 Lewis, An Experiment in Criticism 2024-05-20 McCarthy, All the Pretty Horses 2024-05-10 Dostoyevsky, The Brothers Karamazov 2024-02-02 Thoreau, On the Duty of Civil Disobedience 2024-01-07 Steinbeck, East of Eden 2024-01-02 Hemingway, The Old Man and the Sea 2023-12-27 Hesse,	Siddhartha 2023-12-12 Glass, Words Without Music 2023-12-01 Wylie, Shaka, a pocket biography 2023-11-23 Vonnegut, Slaughterhouse 5 2023-11-10 Deshimaru, The Zen Way to the Martial Arts 2023-10-31 Atwood, The Handmaids Tale 2023-10-23 Solzhenitsyn, One Day In The Life of Ivan Denisovich 2023-10-12 Bird &amp;amp; Sherwin, American Prometheus 2023-10-11 Attia, Outlive 2023-08-13 Krakauer, Into the Wild 2023-07-12 Gallwey, The Inner Game of Tennis 2023-06-25 Meredith, Born in Africa 2023-06-12 Towles, The Lincoln Highway 2023-05-30 Lee, To Kill A Mockingbird 2023-05-23 Bryson, A Walk in the Woods 2023-04-24 Tan Twan Eng, The Gift of Rain 2023-04-04 Bird, Among the Tibetans 2023-04-01 Von Clausewitz, On the Nature of War 2023-03-22 Browder, Freezing Notice 2023-03-15 Burkeman, Four Thousand Weeks 2023-03-04 Jaynes, The Origin of Consciousness in the Breakdown of the Bicameral Mind 2023-02-15 McDougall, Born to Run 2023-02-10 Deutsch, The Beginning of Infinity 2023-01-02 McConaughey, Greenlights 2022-12-30 Woolf, Mrs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>Things on the internet. Perhaps to your taste.
 Argentina on Two Steaks a Day, Maciej Ceglowski Las Torres del Paine, Maciej Ceglowski The Place to Disappear, Susan Orlean Switzerland: The Land of Joyce, Daniel Davies Shipping Out, David Foster Wallace Goodbye to all that, Joan Didion Arrival - Facing the Fear of Existence, Like Stories of Old Paterson - Everyday Virtue &amp;amp; David Foster Wallace - Like Stories of Old E Unibus Plurum: Television and U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/papers/</guid>
      <description>Google scholar
  Kohn TA., Knobel S., Donaldson B., van Boom K., Blackhurst DM., Peart J., Jensen J., Tordiffe A. (2024), Does sex matter in the cheetah? Insights into the skeletal muscle of the fastest land animal, Journal of Experimental Biology, jeb.247284, https://doi.org/10.1242/jeb.247284
  Donaldson BJ., Bezodis NE., Bayne H. (2023), Characterising coordination strategies during initial acceleration in sprinters ranging from highly trained to world class, Journal of Sports Sciences, https://doi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/writing/</guid>
      <description>Just Do 100 Things! After all, there are plenty of people writing badly on the internet, why not me?
1/100
 Chiloe  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
