<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Byron Donaldson</title>
    <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Byron Donaldson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2024, Byron Donaldson</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Field Notes - Cincinnati</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/cincinnati/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/cincinnati/</guid>
      <description>Last updated: 30 Apr 2024
Notes: First impressions of Cincinnati (And the USA) As it happens, in the great year of 2024 I have moved to Cincinnati. Nevermind why, that&amp;rsquo;s my business. Anyway, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d put down some field notes from the first couple of months - first impressions and questions and all that - sort of Devon Zuegel on Miami inspired. These are just the passing observations of an ignorant Southern African, don&amp;rsquo;t take them too seriously - no doubt there will be some prize foolishness throughout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interesting questions, for yourself, and others</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/questions/</guid>
      <description>A good question can be a wonderful thing. Well, I thought I might start a collection! To get better at questions, and to probe more deeply into my own skull, for both general psychic inquiries and more specific situations. If you have good ones, please share them with me! This list will be living. (Source/inspiration provided when known/suitable)
  What important truth do very few people agree with you on?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chiloe</title>
      <link>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/chiloe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byrondonaldson.github.io/posts/chiloe/</guid>
      <description>Chiloé &amp;ldquo;So, what next?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Well, we will go to Chiloé. And it will be good.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I thought we were already in Chile?&amp;rdquo;
I was, by now, used to this kind of total, brutish ignorance. After all, my brother had spent the previous two weeks insisting he could speak Spanish by adding dado to the end of English words. And this from a scientist! At any rate, it didn&amp;rsquo;t matter much, the big man had long since given up creative control over the trip to his reclusive younger brother, and a twenty year out of date Lonely Planet guide to Chile.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
